Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 111, Folder: 11 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Changing Nature of Personnel, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Box: 111, Folder: 12 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Safety Procedure: Crane Operators, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Salaried Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Hourly Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Safe Work Practices for Tool Inspection and Tool Crib Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Rules for Ground Men Working With Cranes or Lift Trucks, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Safe Practices: Rock Bit Division, Colorado Springs Plant, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Safe Work Practices for Phosphating and Shot Blast Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Safe Work Practices for Heat Treat Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Safe Work Practices for Inspection and Assembly Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Safe Work Practices for Toll Room Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Safe Work Practices for Roller Header Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Safe Work Practices for Physical Laboratory Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Safe Work Practices for Material Handling Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Safe Work Practices for Green Turning Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Safe Work Practices for Chrome Plating Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Safe Work Practices for Maintenance Department Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Safe Work Practices for Welding Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: Safe Work Practices for Boiler House Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Safety at Work, at Home, at Play, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Insurance Plan for Salaried and Eligible Hourly Paid Employees of The Timken Company, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: Safe Work Practices for Grinding Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Safe Working Practices for Cage Stamping Operations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: A History of The Timken Company, Publication (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Box: 112, Folder: 1 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Report On Replies to a Questionnaire Addressed to all Members of the Organization of Six or More Months of Service, Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    November. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Report On Replies To A Questionnaire Addressed To All New Members of the Organization Who Entered Between March 1946 and September 1946, Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    February. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: My Association with The Todd Company, Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Inter-Office Correspondence, Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    By Walter L. Todd. April 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ourline of Cooperative Plan to provide Insured Retirement Annuities for Eligible Employees of The Todd Company, Inc., Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
    January 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Cooperative Group Insurance Plan for The General Offices and Rochester Manufacturing Divisions of The Todd Company, Inc., Publication (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Box: 112, Folder: 2 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Landing Craft Infantry (Large), Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: At War, Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    June. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Todd Shipyards Corporation Retirement System, Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: To Employees:, Publication (Box 112, Folder 2)
    August 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 3 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Tokheim Family, Publication (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Box: 112, Folder: 4 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Toledo Plan For Industrial Harmony, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    By Morton Goldberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How Toledo's LMC Works, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    By Jerome Gross. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Toledo Chamber of Commerce, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Toledo City Journal, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    January 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: TIDC's First Year, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    By William L. Batt, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Toledo Pioneers for Peace Industrial Relations Charter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    February 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Area Pension Plan Perks Up, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
    November 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Toledo's Plan For Labor Peace A study of the Labor-Management-Citizens Committee, Publication (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Box: 112, Folder: 5 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Professional Staff Handbook, Publication (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Box: 112, Folder: 6 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The National Welfare of 140 Million Americans, Publication (Box 112, Folder 6)
    By Allen W. Rucker. June 26. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 7 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Organizations Their Types Objectives and Activities, Publication (Box 112, Folder 7)
    October 21. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 8 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Job Methods Training, Publication (Box 112, Folder 8)
    October. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Job Relations Training, Publication (Box 112, Folder 8)
    January. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Instructor Training, Publication (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Box: 112, Folder: 9 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ratification of Union Contracts The "Pros and Cons", Publication (Box 112, Folder 9)
    April. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Strikes, Public Pays!, Publication (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Shipper Pays The Proposed Six-Hour Day For Railroad Labor, Publication (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Box: 112, Folder: 10 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Complete Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 10)
    July 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Box: 112, Folder: 11 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Periodic Progress Report, Publication (Box 112, Folder 11)
    September. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 12 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing and Bonus Systems As Applied to Trucks Trailers Taxi and Bus Lines, Publication (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Box: 112, Folder: 13 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Trundle Talks No. 110 Markets and Prices, Publication (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Box: 112, Folder: 14 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Can Labor and Management Work Together?, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    By Osgood Nichols and T. R. Carskadon. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    June 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    June 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    June 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    June 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    July 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    July 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    August 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: United States Steel Corporation Quarterly Earnings Report-September 20, 1953, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    October 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    April 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    May 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    December 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News From The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    January 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 25: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 27: Newsbriefs A Clipsheet, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 28: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 29: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 30: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 31: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 32: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 33: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 34: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 35: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 36: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 37: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 38: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 39: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 40: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 41: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 42: Newsletter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 43: Strikes and Democratic Government A Report by the Labor Committee of The Twentieth Century Fund, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 44: The Round Table, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Item 45: Facts About Labor and National Defense, Publication (Box 112, Folder 14)
    May. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 15 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 112, Folder 15)
    August-September. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 112, Folder 15)
    October-November. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 16 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 16)
    July 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Profit-Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Box: 112, Folder: 17 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement, Death Benefit and Savings Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 17)
    December 16. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 18 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Stellite Story, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: at Carbide, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance For California Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    June 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Trefoil, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    May 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Stockholder Briefs, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Union Carbide World, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    July. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union Carbide World, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Oak Ridge National Laboratory, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    April 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The West Virginia Hillbilly, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    September 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Carbide News, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    February 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Carbide News, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Union Carbide in Nuclear Energy, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Riverviews, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: The Forecaster, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    April 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Trefoil, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    April 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Carbidea Courier, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Texas City Carbide News, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: The Carbide Californian, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    November 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Tapping Company, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
    March. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Institute Plant, Publication (Box 112, Folder 18)
- Box: 112, Folder: 19 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Historical Summary, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: People Planning the Future with People, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    August. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Union Carbide's 20 Years In Nuclear Energy, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Background Information on Union Carbide Corporation, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    May 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Highest Self-Interest, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    By F. Perry Wilson. November 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Growth of Union Carbide Corporation and Its Divisions, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    October 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Health Care and Disability Benefits Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Savings Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Our History, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: The Union Carbide Corporate Charter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Environmental Update II, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Our History, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Major Medical Expense Plan Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: About Carbide, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Information for Employees in the New York General Offices, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: about Carbide, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: The Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Major Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: the Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans for Hospitalization and Surgical-Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 21: The Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 22: Savings Plan For Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 23: Pension Benefits and Disability Benefits Under Non-Contributory Pension Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 24: Summary of Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 25: Layoff Allowance Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    October 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Employee Participation In Military Programs, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 27: Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 28: Educational Refund Policy, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 29: your Savings Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 30: your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
    July 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: your Group Insurance Plan Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 32: Hospital-Surgical-Medical, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Item 33: your Major Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 112, Folder 19)
- Box: 112, Folder: 20 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Salary Payments During Disability Absence, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Union Carhide Plastics Company, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Employment Application, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: National Carbon Company history products organization, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: The Power of Niagara Falls in Metals and Chemicals, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Research at Union Carbide, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Research at Union Carbide, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: "The Carbide" A Pioneer Industry of the Soo, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Products and Processes, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Mesa Miracle In ColoradoUtah New MexicoArizonaWyoming, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Hot-Metal Magic, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Discovery, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Carbide's New Look, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
    September 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Motion Pictures from Union Carbide The Discovery Company, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: Precedent Value of Labor Arbitration Awards, Publication (Box 112, Folder 20)
    By Charles T. Doyle. Item is in English.
- Box: 112, Folder: 21 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Union Electric News, Publication (Box 112, Folder 21)
- Box: 112, Folder: 22 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Book of Information Guidance and Instruction, Publication (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The Birth and Development of The Union Labor Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 112, Folder 22)
    By Matthew Woll, Carville D. Benson. March 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Union Labor Life Insurance Company Its By Laws, Publication (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Union Labor Life Insurance Company Its Charter, Publication (Box 112, Folder 22)
- Box: 112, Folder: 23 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Capital and the Welfare State, Publication (Box 112, Folder 23)
    By Reese H. Taylor. December 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Relations Policies and Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 112, Folder 23)
- Box: 112, Folder: 24 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Union Pacific Railroad Company and The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreeement Between Union Pacific Railroad Company and All That Class of Clerks and Other Office, Station and Stores Employes Represented by the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employes, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Union Pacific Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen Representing Signal Department Employes Classified Herein, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    April 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Agreement between Union Pacific Railroad Company and The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between Union Pacific Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Railroad Signalment of America Representing Signal Department Employes Classified Herein, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Yardmen Represented by the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    September 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Before Joint Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By R. S. Lovett. March 19-20. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Statement of R. S. Lovett Before the Texas Welfare Commission, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By R. S. Lovett. May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Valuation of Railroad Property Before the Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By R. S. Lovett. December 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Comments on Some of the Methods Suggested for Solving the Railroad Problem, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By R. S. Lovett. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Return of the Railroads to Private Ownership, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By R. S. Lovett. August 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Statement of Mr. Lovett Before The Newlands Joint Committee, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    By Robert S. Lovett. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Agreement Between Union Pacific Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters Governing Rates of Pay and Working Conditions of Chair Car Attendants, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 14: Scheudle of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Waiters, Bar Waiters, Pantrymen, Lounge and Parlor Car Porters, Porter-Waiters, Porter-Waiters-in-Charge, Waiters-in-Charge and Stationary Pantrymen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Employes of the Classes in I. Dining, Caf-Lounge, Caf-Club, Caf-Observation, Caf, and Coach Buffet Cars II. Boarding Outfits III. Hotels and Restaurants, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 16: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Employes of the Classes Represented By The American Train Dispatchers Associations, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    June 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company for the territory Los Angeles-Salt Lake City, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
    July 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Schedule of Rules governing Wages and Working Conditions of Conductors, Brakement and Train Baggagement, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Item 19: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company for the terrirtory Granger-Huntington Salt Lake - Butte and the Order of Railway Conductors, Publication (Box 112, Folder 24)
- Box: 112, Folder: 25 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Union Pacific Railroad Company and The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
    February 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Agreement Between The Union Pacific Railroad Company and the American Railway Supervisors Association, Incorporated, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Schedule of Rules Governing the Working Conditions of Machinists, Boilermakers, Blacksmiths, Sheet Metal Workers and Molders, Electrical Workers, Carmen, and their Helpers and Apprentices, and Coach Clearners, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Schedule of Rules Governing the Working Conditions of Stationary Engineers, Firemen and Oilers, and Railway Shop Laborers, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company for the territory Salt Lake City - Butte Granger - Huntington Brotherhood of Locomotive, Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
    Ocotber 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Yardmen Represented by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Dining Car Stewards, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Yardmen Represented by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions for Brakemen and Train Baggagemen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
    October 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Agreement between the Union Pacific Railroad Company for the territory Lost Angeles - Salt Lake City And its Conductors Represented by the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, Publication (Box 112, Folder 25)
    November 16. Item is in English.